gvtube.com 2011-01-20

# GotVoice Privacy Policy

[](http://www.truste.org/ivalidate.php?url=www.gotvoice.com&sealid=101)GotVoice is committed to protecting your privacy. GotVoice is a general audience web site, intended for users over the age of 13. Personal information of all users is collected, used and disclosed as described in this Privacy Statement. 

**Collection of your Personal Information**

GotVoice collects information during the registration process, including first and last name, country, region or state, zip or postal code, email addresses, credit card number and billing address, phone number(s), PIN and Telecommunication Carriers. You may update your registration information at any time from within your GotVoice account by clicking the "Phones" button on the navigation bar. 

GotVoice stores, transmits, processes and maintains your messages, contact lists, addressee’ and other data related to your account in order to provide the service to You. 

GotVoice may collect information about your visit, including the pages You view, the links You click and other actions taken within GotVoice. We also collect certain standard information that your browser sends to every website You visit, such as your IP address, browser type and language, access times and referring Web site addresses. 

Certain GotVoice services may be co-branded and offered in conjunction with another company. If You register for or use such services, both GotVoice and the other company may receive information collected in conjunction with the co-branded services. 

**Use of your Personal Information**

  * Your registration information is used to operate the site, for demographic statistics, and to display appropriate individualized advertisements. 
  * New users will receive a GotVoice welcome email explaining the features provided by the service. GotVoice may also send periodic member letters, from which You may not unsubscribe without closing your account, to announce important service changes, new features, technical issue updates and information about other products and services. 
  * GotVoice maintains and processes your GotVoice account and its contents to provide the GotVoice service to You and to improve our services. The GotVoice service may include relevant advertising and related links based on the IP address, content of messages and other information related to your use of GotVoice. 
  * GotVoice processes the information in your messages for various purposes, including delivering the message, delivering advertisements and related links, backing up your messages, making your voicemail searchable and other purposes relating to offering You GotVoice. GotVoice and its partners may use the content of Your messages to improve message processing capabilities. 
  * GotVoice may send You information related to your GotVoice account or other GotVoice services. 

**Information sharing and onward transfer**

  * When You send voice messages, GotVoice may include information such as your phone number and email address as part of the message. 
  * We provide advertisers only aggregated non-personal information such as the number of times one of their ads was clicked. We do not sell, rent or otherwise share your personal information with any third parties except in the limited circumstances described herein, such as when we believe we are required to do so by law. 

GotVoice also uses your personal information to inform You of other products or services available from GotVoice. GotVoice may also send You surveys regarding current services or potential new services that may be offered. We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as handling the processing and delivery of mailings, providing customer support, processing transactions, or performing statistical analysis of our services. We will only provide those companies the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information and are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose. Personal information collected on this site may be stored and processed in the United States and by using this site, You consent to any such transfer of information. GotVoice abides by the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data.

**Control of your Personal Information**

You may choose not to receive marketing material from GotVoice or on behalf of external third party business partners. You may also stop the delivery of future promotional e-mail from GotVoice by following the specific instructions in the e-mail You receive. The instructions explain how to stop receiving such e-mails. 

GotVoice sends out periodic e-mails informing You of technical service issues, product surveys, new feature announcements and news about GotVoice products and services. You will not be able to unsubscribe to these mailings, as they are considered a part of the service You have chosen. 

You may have the ability to view or edit your personal information, if You have a billing account You can add to or update the information by emailing customer support at info@gotvoice.com. 

**Security of your Personal Information**

GotVoice is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information You provide on computer systems with limited access, which are located in controlled facilities. When we transmit highly confidential information (such as a credit card number) over the Internet, we protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol. 

**Use of Cookies** GotVoice uses "cookies" to help You personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to You, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to You. 

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save You time. For example, if You register with GotVoice, a cookie helps GotVoice to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, preferred email address, and so on. When You return to GotVoice, the information You previously provided can be retrieved, so You can easily use the GotVoice features that You customized. 

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but You can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if You prefer. If You choose to decline cookies, You may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the GotVoice. 

**Use of Web Beacons** GotVoice Web pages may contain electronic images known as Web beacons - sometimes called single-pixel gifs - that allow GotVoice to count users who have visited those pages and to deliver co-branded services. GotVoice may include Web beacons in promotional e-mail messages or GotVoice Newsletters in order to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon. 

GotVoice may also place Web beacons from third parties on our site in order to compile aggregated statistics and to help determine the effectiveness of our joint promotional or advertising campaigns. GotVoice prohibits Web beacons on our site from being used by third parties to access your personal information. 

**Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites, Ad Servers, and Sponsors**

Some of our sites contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Visitors should consult the other sites' privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

GotVoice sometimes may offer content (e.g., contests, sweepstakes, or promotions) that is sponsored by or co-branded with identified third parties. By virtue of these relationships, the third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the site activity. GotVoice has no control over these third parties' use of this information. 

GotVoice may use a reputable third party to present or serve the advertisements that you may see at its Web pages. These third party ad servers may use cookies, web beacons, clear .gifs or similar technologies to help present such advertisements, and to help measure and research the advertisements' effectiveness. The use of these technologies by these third party ad servers is subject to their own privacy policies and is not covered by our privacy policy. For more information on this site's use of such third-party ad servers, please click here.

**Enforcement of this Privacy Statement**

GotVoice is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build user’s trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers the Web site [www.GotVoice.com.](http://www.gotvoice.com/) Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe. 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact [support@GotVoice.com.](mailto:support@GotVoice.com) If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should contact TRUSTe at <http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php>TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns. 

**Changes to this Statement**

GotVoice will occasionally update this Privacy Statement to reflect company and customer feedback. When GotVoice posts changes to this Statement, they will be indicated by the date of the last update on our website. If there are material changes to this Statement or in how GotVoice will use your personal information, GotVoice will prominently post such changes prior to implementing the change. GotVoice encourages You to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how GotVoice is protecting your information. 

**Contact Information**

GotVoice welcomes your comments regarding this Privacy Statement. If You believe that GotVoice has not adhered to this Statement, please contact GotVoice by e-mail, or postal mail. 

_GotVoice Privacy  
GotVoice Corporation  
10512 NE 68th Street   
Kirkland, WA 98033_
